sendmygift.com 2016-06-26

# Send Online Gifts to your friends and relatives in India Customer Login Send Online Gifts to your friends and relatives in India

All the information you enter on our site is confidential. We do not sell your information nor do we share it with anyone. We are a family owned and operated business with the highest degree of integrity. Your information is safe with us. We respect your concern over your right to privacy, for a secure online shopping experience. By visiting any website operated by the association (collectively referred to as the "Site"), you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

## Information collected while surfing our website:

The information we capture from users of our site, allows us to personalize and continually improve your online experience, making it easier and more enjoyable. The information we collect is as below :

  * **Automated Information**

We receive and store certain type of information whenever you interact with us.  
For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your web browser accesses our site. Cookies are pieces of data your web browser stores on your hard drive to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but most allow you to instruct your browser to prevent the use of cookies. However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of our site, such as the shopping basket, will not function properly.

  * **Information you share with us**

We receive and store all the information you enter on the site which is automated, or share with us on the call, email and chat.  
For example, when you order from the site, we collect the following information: your name, telephone number, email address, billing information (credit card number, expiry date and billing address), products purchased, and the recipient´s name, address and telephone number.

**Note:** In some cases, the recipient may be contacted via telephone to schedule delivery. Also, if you register as a member, we request your name, address, phone number, email address and other information as set forth in the membership form. You can choose not to provide certain information, but then you might not be able to take advantage of many of the features of the Site. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, processing your orders and communicating with you.

  * **Information from Other Sources**

For reasons such as improving personalization of our service, we might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information.

**Does  We Share The Information It Receives?**

We do not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information that visitors submit to our Site. 

We may utilize your personally identifiable information to send you information or materials we think you will find interesting. However, at the time of collection, you will typically have the option of instructing us not to send you additional information or share your personal information with business partners or advertisers. We are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of our advertisers or business partners and encourages you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other Web site.

We may use reputable third parties to manage activities available on our Site including Web hosting, database management and order processing and authentication. These parties may have access to personally identifiable information submitted by visitors who participate in those activities. We instructs these third parties to use personally identifiable information only for the specific purpose for which it is collected, and not to sell, market or transfer such information to other entities except as needed to provide the designated services.

**How Secure Is Information About Me?**

We maintains appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of personally identifiable information submitted to our sites, and periodically reviews and updates its security measures in light of current technologies. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be totally secure. Although the we strives to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warranty the security of any information you may transmit to us or from our online products and services. Once we do receive your transmission, however, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. We use VeriSign as our SSL (Secure Socket Layer) digital certificate provider, providing our customers the strongest certificate services available. When credit card information is transmitted, industry standard encryption is used.

**About Children**

We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet. Pursuant to the Children´s Online Protection Act of 1998, the Association will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent.

**Links to Third Party and Co-Branded Sites**

We may have and continues to establish relationships with other Web sites that allow visitors to the Site to link directly to these third party Web sites. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices and content of these third party Web sites. When interacting with any third party site, we encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user terms and conditions whenever interacting with, and prior to providing any personal information to, any the third party Web site.
